{
    "subject": "resource/Christopher_Reid_(entertainer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Rapping",
    "human_readable": "Christopher Reid's occupation is rapping.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.579601526260376,
            "question": "What does Christopher Reid do as a profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4477320909500122,
            "question": "What is Christopher Reid's profession in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43362170457839966,
            "question": "What is Christopher Reid known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3531262278556824,
            "question": "What is Christopher Reid best known for doing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34086519479751587,
            "question": "Is Christopher Reid a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3057080805301666,
            "question": "What is Christopher Reid's primary career path?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3047682046890259,
            "question": "How would you describe Christopher Reid's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2618752717971802,
            "question": "What type of artist is Christopher Reid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20970135927200317,
            "question": "What genre of music is associated with Christopher Reid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16525347530841827,
            "question": "Which musical style does Christopher Reid practice?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Christopher Reid's occupation is rapping.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7909_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is associated with Christopher Reid?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7909_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of artist is Christopher Reid?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7909_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Christopher Reid's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7909_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7909_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Christopher Reid, including his profession as a rapper, actor, and comedian. The text from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7909/re-ranker-msmarco/16.txt mentions that Reid \"is an American rapper, actor and comedian.\" This information supports the statement that Christopher Reid's occupation is rapping."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Christopher Reid has been an American rapper, as evidenced by his work with the rap duo Kid 'n Play and his role in releasing albums. Therefore, supporting the triple that Christopher Reid's occupation includes rapping."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}